Walter B. Wriston Papers MS134
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1925 -- 2004; 1932 -- 1977; MS134.006; 2.2 Linear Feet; 49 Digital Object(s)
  - Walter B. Wriston with his grandson, Christopher W. Quintal, 1984; MS134.006.035.00029; Unknown (Box 35)
    This picture was taken in Walter B. Wriston's office in Citicorp Center. The print and digital image were created from 'File3122' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 6'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Quintal, Barbara Catherine; Quintal, Christopher W.
  - Walter B. Wriston, Senator Edward M. Kennedy, and Wesleyan University notables, 1984-06; MS134.006.035.00030; Unknown (Box 35)
    Left to Right: Colin Campbell, President of Wesleyan; Senator Edward M. Kennedy; David McCullough; Natalie Zemon Davis; Walter B. Wriston; Nicholas John Turro, Jr.; and D. Ronald Daniel, Board Chairman of Wesleyan University Trustees. The print and digital image were created from 'File2800' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Campbell, Colin; Kennedy, Edward M.; McCullough, David; Davis, Natalie Zemon; Turro, Nicholas John Jr.; Daniel, D. Ronald
  - Walter B. Wriston in his office at Citicorp Center after his retirement, 1984; MS134.006.035.00031; Unknown (Box 35)
    This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The print and digital image were created from 'File2645' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 4'.
  - President Ronald Reagan, Walter B. Wriston, and members of the Economic Policy Committee, 1985; MS134.006.035.00032; Unknown (Box 35)
    Picture taken in the White House Roosevelt Room. The print and digital image were created from 'File2906' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 5'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Reagan, Ronald
  - Walter B. Wriston shaking hands with President Ronald Reagan, 1985; MS134.006.035.00033; Unknown (Box 35)
    The print and digital image were created from 'File2825' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 3'.
  - President George H.W. Bush and Walter B. Wriston in the Vice President's Office in the White House, 1991; MS134.006.035.00034; Unknown (Box 35)
    The print and digital image were created from 'File2908' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 5'.
    photographic print; Bush, George H.W.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston with his granddaughter, Barbara Catherine Quintal, 1994; MS134.006.035.00035; Unknown (Box 35)
    This picture was taken on the Wriston Farm in Connecticut. The print and digital image were created from 'File3123' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 6'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Quintal, Barbara Catherine
  - Walter B. Wriston after his retirement from Citibank/Citicorp, 1997; MS134.006.035.00036; Unknown (Box 35)
    This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The print and digital image were created from 'File2644' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 4'.
  - Walter B. Wriston and Kathryn Dineen Wriston in Florida, 1997; MS134.006.035.00037; Unknown (Box 35)
    The print and digital image were created from 'File2801' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
  - Walter B. Wriston with his wife and extended family, 1999; MS134.006.035.00038; Unknown (Box 35)
    Left to Right: Walter B. Wriston; Barbara Catherine Quintal (Walter B. Wriston's granddaughter); Christopher W. Quintal (Walter B. Wriston's grandson); Catherine Wriston Quintal (Walter B. Wriston's daughter); Richard Quintal (Walter B. Wriston's son-in-law) In front: Kathryn Dineen Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's wife). The print and digital image were created from 'File2802' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Kathryn Dineen; Quintal, Barbara Catherine; Quintal, Christopher W.; Quintal, Catherine Wriston; Quintal, Richard
  - Walter B. Wriston, 2004; MS134.006.035.00039; Leynse, James (Box 35)
    This image is copyrighted to James Leynse. The print was created from 'File2799' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
  - Walter B. Wriston, President Richard M. Nixon, and other members of the National Commission on Productivity in The White House Cabinet Room, 1970 -- 1974; MS134.006.035.00040 (Box MS134 Shared 6)
    This oversize print was donated by Kathryn Wriston in summer 2009. The photograph appears to have been taken on the same day at the image MS134/006-035:00023.
    photographic print; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-; Wriston, Walter B.; United States. White House.
  - Walter and Kathryn Wriston with President Jimmy Carter, 1990 -- 1995; MS134.006.035.00041 (Box MS134 Shared 6)
    This print was donated by Kathryn Wriston in summer 2009.
  - Walter B. Wriston and Laurent Jacque, Chair of International Business Relations, 2001; MS134.006.035.00042; Unknown
    Scanned from original in Laurent Jacque's office at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Jacque, Laurent
  - George S. Moore and Walter B. Wriston, 1967; MS134.006.035.00043; Unknown
    George S. Moore, Chairman of First National City Bank and Walter B. Wriston, President and CEO of First National City Bank. This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'L1000007' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
    Moore, George S.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston and his wife, Kathryn Dineen Wriston, 2001; MS134.006.035.00044; Unknown
    The image was created from 'Photograph (2)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Kathryn Dineen
  - Walter B. Wriston and his wife, Kathryn Dineen Wriston, 1973; MS134.006.035.00045; Unknown
    The image was created from 'Photograph (10)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
  - Walter B. Wriston in his office as Chairman and CEO of Citibank and Citigroup, 1976; MS134.006.035.00046; Unknown
    His office was located at 399 Park Ave, NY. This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'Photograph (16)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
    Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston in his office in front of a portrait of Thomas Gresham, 1983; MS134.006.035.00047; Unknown
    An image of Thomas Gresham appears on the wall. This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'Photograph (18)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
  - Walter B. Wriston at a meeting of the Commission on Privitization, 1987; MS134.006.035.00048; Unknown
    David F. Linowes, Chairman of President Reagan's Commission on Privitization, Walter B. Wriston, and Richard H. Fink. The image was created from 'Photograph (20)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
    Wriston, Walter B.-- Fink, Richard H.; Linowes, David F.
  - George P. Shultz, Walter B. Wriston, Paul McCracken, and Alan Greenspan in a meeting, 1985; MS134.006.035.00049; Unknown
    Clockwise from left; George P. Shultz, Walter B. Wriston, Unidentified Man, Unidentified Man, Unidentified Man, Paul McCracken, Alan Greenspan, and Unidentified Man. The image was created from 'Photograph (22)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
    Shultz, George P.; Wriston, Walter B.; McCracken, Paul; Greenspan, Alan
  - Walter B. Wriston with his wife and extended family, 1990; MS134.006.035.00050; Unknown
    Back Row: Kathryn Dineen Wriston, Walter B. Wriston, and Christopher W. Quintal Front Row: Barbara Catherine 'Katy' Quintal, Richard Quintal, and Catherine Wriston Quintal. The image was created from 'Photograph (27)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
    Wriston, Kathryn Dineen; Wriston, Walter B.; Quintal, Christopher W.; Quintal, Barbara Catherine; Quintal, Richard Quintal; Wriston, Catherine
  - Walter B. Wriston and extended family, 1989; MS134.006.035.00051; Unknown
    Left to Right: Christopher W. Quintal, Kathryn Dineen Wriston, Catherine Wriston Quintal holding Barbara Catherine 'Katy' Quintal, Richard Quintal, and Walter B. Wriston. The image was created from 'Photograph (32)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
    Quintal, Christopher W.; Wriston, Kathryn Dineen; Quintal, Catherine Wriston; Quintal, Barbara Catherine; Quintal, Richard; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston and Kathryn Dineen Wriston in the mountains, 1990; MS134.006.035.00052; Unknown
    The image was created from 'Photograph (34)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
    Teton Range (Wyo. and Idaho); Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Kathryn Dineen
  - President Ronald Reagan with Walter B. Wriston in Oval Office, 1981; MS134.006.035.00053; Unknown
    Left to Right: Paul W. McCracken, Alan Greenspan, President Ronald Reagan, George P. Schultz, and Walter B. Wriston during a meeting of the Economic Policy Advisory Board in the Oval Office. The image was created from 'Photograph 21' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7'.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Cracken, Paul W.; Greenspan, Alan; Reagan, Ronald; Shultz, George P.
  - Walter Wriston in blue suit and tie, 1967; MS134.006.035.00054; Unknown
  - Photographs on CD, 1925 -- 2004; MS134.006.036 (Box 36)
    These are the eight CDs from which photographic prints were made. See Box 035 for prints.
- Awards and Recognitions, 1961 -- 2006; MS134.007; 3.6 Linear Feet; 2 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains awards and other materials recognizing the service and achievements of Walter B. Wriston. Wriston's awards include the Order of the Golden Heart conferred by President Ferdinand E. Marcos and Mrs. Imelda R. Marcos in 1971 and the Presidential Medal of Freedom conferred by President George W. Bush in 2004. There is also a framed collage of material from Wriston's 1961 visit to the White House to meet with President John F. Kennedy. There is a framed congratulatory letter from President Ronald Reagan presented to Wriston upon his retirement from Citibank, as well as a framed photograph of Wriston with President Reagan. There are two framed letters of condolence from President George W. Bush, written to Kathryn Wriston upon the death of Walter Wriston.
  The materials in this series are arranged as received.
  - Order of the Golden Heart shadow box, 1971; MS134.007.037.00001 (Box MS134 Shared 6)
    This shadow box contains Walter B. Wriston's Order of the Golden Heart (2 medals and a ribbon to be worn around the neck). It was presented to Wriston on October 29, 1971 by President Ferdinand E. Marcos and Mrs. Imelda R. Marcos at a ceremony at the Malacanang Palace.
  - Group photograph including Walter B. Wriston and President Ronald Reagan, 1984; MS134.007.043.00001 (Box MS134 Shared 5)
    This framed photograph was probably presented to Wriston by President Reagan upon his retirement from Citigroup in 1984. The mat of the photograph includes a note from President Reagan to Wriston.
  - Cartoon Tribute to Walter B. Wriston, 2000-10; MS134.007.043.00002 (Box MS134 Shared 5)
    This framed drawing highlights Wriston's career achievements in a cartoon format. It was created by the Center for Business Innovation for their meeting/conference 'Measuring the Future: Navigating the New Economy', October 1-3, 2000.
  - Letters of condolence from President George W. Bush upon the death of Walter B. Wriston, 2006-01-25 -- 2006-01-26; MS134.007.044.00001 (Box 44)
    These two framed letters were written by President George W. Bush to Kathryn Wriston, expressing condolences upon the death of Walter B. Wriston.
  - Letter from President Ronald Reagan to Walter B. Wriston, 1984-07-11; MS134.007.044.00002 (Box 44)
    This framed letter was written by President Ronald Reagan to Walter B. Wriston, congratulating Wriston upon his retirement from Citigroup in 1984.
  - Certificate awarding the Presidential Medal of Freedom to Walter B. Wriston, 2004-06-23; MS134.007.044.00003 (Box 44)
    This framed certificate awards the Presidential Medal of Freedom to Walter B. Wriston from President George W. Bush on June 23, 2004.
  - Collage of White House Memorabilia documenting Walter B. Wriston's visit, 1961-06-30; MS134.007.044.00004 (Box 44)
    This framed collage includes memorabilia from Walter B. Wriston's visit to the White House to meet President John F. Kennedy on June 30, 1961. Materials in the collage include a place card, matchbook, and telegram of invitation.
- Computer Spreadsheets, 2006; MS134.008; 0.25 Linear Feet
  This series consists of spreadsheets printed and annotated by Kathryn Wriston which document the original order of the files on each of the three computers ('CT MAC', 'NYC MAC', and 'IBM') used by Walter B. Wriston, as well as relevant metadata such as file size, type, date, etc. Printed-out computer files were arranged into other series for ease of access, but each printed-out computer file can be intellectually traced back to its original computer context using the spreadsheets. Drafts of the same document may appear on multiple computers, but do not always have the same title or file name. Individual documents were organized using the final publication title, when available. However, each folder also retains the original file title which, in turn, corresponds to the title listed in the spreadsheets.
  This series is not arranged.
  - Computer Spreadsheets, 2006; MS134.008.041.00072 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
- Additional accessions, 1970 -- 1995; MS134.009; 7.2 Linear Feet
  This series includes three boxes of duplicate videocassettes, audiocassettes, CDs, DVDs, floppy disks, and paper materials that exist elsewhere in the Walter B. Wriston papers.
  Also included are the manuscript for The Independent Man Beckons Still, 1982, and related correspondence with publishers, 1984; and speeches, 1982-1987.
  Also included are four invitations to White House dinners, 1973-1981; invitations to other black tie events, 1972-1983; two letters from President Gerald R. Ford, 1974; and letters to Wriston, 1972-1991. Photographs include Wriston with the Prince and Princess de Bourbon, Spain and George Moore, 1973; a meeting of President Richard Nixon's Labor Management Advisory Committee of the National Commission for Industrial Peace in the Cabinet room with the President, 1973; and Meet the Press program and photograph, April 20, 1975.
  - Duplicate Videocassettes, MS134-001 (Box data_value_missing_d9c8fdc8ee1ee4bba1595f123168a5d8, Box 1)
    This box contains unprocessed material in VHS format that already exists in the Walter Wriston papers. As of December 2009, all the material in this box is duplicated elsewhere in the collection.
  - Duplicate DVDs and CDs, MS134-002 (Box data_value_missing_d9c8fdc8ee1ee4bba1595f123168a5d8, Box 2)
    This box contains unprocessed material in DVD and CD format that already exists in the Walter Wriston papers. For material in DVD and CD formats to be considered a duplicate, the material in the collection must also exist in a DVD or CD format. When the pre-existing material was not in a DVD or CD format, the items were added to the collection, even if that duplicated content. As of December 2009, all the material in this box is duplicated elsewhere in the collection.
  - Duplicate Videocassettes, Audiocassettes, CDs, DVDs, Floppy Disks, and Paper Materials, MS134-003 (Box data_value_missing_435a4996dd1c61243a111d800cb39cf1, Box 3)
    This box contains unprocessed videocassettes, audiocassettes, CDs, DVDs, floppy disks, and paper materials that already exists in the Walter Wriston papers. For material in DVD and CD formats to be considered a duplicate, the material in the collection must also exist in a DVD or CD format. When the pre-existing material was not in a DVD or CD format, the items were added to the collection, even if that duplicated content. The CDs of computer files from Walter B. Wriston's computers were printed out by Kathryn Wriston and processed into the collection. The content of the floppy disks is inaccessible. As of December 2009, all the material in this box is duplicated elsewhere in the collection.
  - Ephemera, 1973 -- 1981; MS134-004 (Box 1, Box 4)
    Four invitations to White House dinners, 1973-1981; invitations to other black tie events, 1975-1977; two letters from President Gerald R. Ford, 1974; matchbook from The President's House; and Meet the Press program and photograph, April 20, 1975.
  - Memorabilia and manuscripts, 1970 -- 1995; MS134-005 (Box data_value_missing_1ef9ff621a2c67b5325574427ecaa437, Box 5)
    Manuscript for The Independent Man Beckons Still, 1982, and related correspondence with publishers, 1984; speeches, 1982-1987; letters to Wriston, 1972-1991; invitations, 1972-1983; and two photographs: Wriston with the Prince and Princess de Bourbon, Spain and George Moore, 1973, and a meeting of President Richard Nixon's Labor Management Advisory Committee of the National Commission for Industrial Peace in the Cabinet room with the President, 1973.